{
    "_comment": "Each entry consists of a prompt and a list of answers.",

    "data": [

        {
            "prompt": "Who created Serenity OS?",
            "answer": 1,
            "answers": [
                "Linus Groh",
                "Andreas Kling",
                "Ali Mohammadpur"
            ]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "In what year was the Serenity GitHub repository created?",
            "answer": 3,
            "answers": [
                "2017",
                "2019",
                "2020",
                "2018"
            ]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "9 + 10 = ?",
            "answer": 0,
            "answers": [
                "21",
                "19",
                "910",
                "64"
            ]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "In the UK, the abbreviation NHS stands for National what Service?",
            "answer": 1,
            "answers": [
                "Humanitany",
                "Health",
                "Honour",
                "Household"
            ]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "Which Disney character famously leaves a glass slipper behind at a royal ball?",
            "answer": 3,
            "answers": [
                "Pocahontas",
                "Cinderella",
                "Elsa",
                "Sleeping Beauty"
            ]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "A person with well-developed abdominal muscles is said to have a what?",
            "answer": 1,
            "answers": [
                "One-pack",
                "Six-pack",
                "12-pack",
                "Family-pack"
            ]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "In fancy hotels, it is traditional for what tantalizing treat to be left on your pillow?",
            "answer": 2,
            "answers": [
                "A pretzel",
                "An apple",
                "A mint",
                "A lolipop"
            ]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "If someone asked to see your ID, what might you show them?",
            "answer": 1,
            "answers": [
                "Your tongue",
                "Your passport",
                "Your teeth",
                "The door"
            ]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "What was William Shakespeare's first play?",
            "answer": 3,
            "answers": [
                "Richard III",
                "The Comedy of Errors",
                "Romeo and Juliet",
                "The Two Gentlemen of Verona"
            ]
        },
        {
            "prompt": "In which year was the Second Sino-Japaneese War?",
            "answer": 0,
            "answers": [
                "1937",
                "1940",
                "1935",
                "1933"
            ]
        }

    ]
}
